metronomeonline.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy - METRONOME ONLINE - free online metronome

### PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OUR SERVICE.

Metronome Online is committed to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information and dissemination practices for Metronome Online Website and iOS/Android app:

Metronome Online does not sell, market, rent, trade, or otherwise share personally identifiable information with any third party. Metronome Online may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. Metronome Online may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user and project agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Metronome Online, our users, or others.

Metronome Online is committed to fully complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and does not accept registration or any type of personally identifiable information from children younger than 13 years of age. We urge children to check with their parents before entering information on any Website and we encourage parents to discuss with their kids the restrictions regarding the online release of personal information to anyone they don’t know.

Metronome Online Website might contain links to other Websites. Metronome Online makes no representations whatsoever about any other Website accessed through Metronome Online Site. Metronome Online has no control over the content of non-Metronome Online Websites, even if they contain the Metronome Online’ logo. In addition, a link to a non-Metronome Online Website does not mean that Metronome Online endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content, or the safety of use, of such a Website.

### REGISTRATION

Our registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name) and unique identifiers (like their email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to provide services on the Website and to send the user information about our products, company, and valuable music-related content from our writers or some of our partners. Users have a choice to opt-in to receive such newsletters. The customer’s contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary, for critical app updates. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Opt-In/Out section below. Your email address is necessary as a unique identifier when you create an account. All information you provide, including your email address, is uniquely identifying and is not shared with anyone outside Metronome Online.

### CHANGING PERSONAL INFORMATION

If you wish to change any of the personal information that you completed when you registered on Metronome Online, click the “Profile” link once you sign in on the Website. You then get to a page that allows you to update personal information including email address, name and password, and all other options.

This site has security measures in place to ensure that personally identifiable information collected in the future is secure, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers as well as electronic security systems.  We use MediaTemple as a hosting provider, with servers inside the United States.

By using our Website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Metronome Online. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### COOKIES

Our website uses cookies, information files that your Web browser places on your computer for the duration of your visit to a Website. Metronome Online uses Cookies for keeping your session active and for personalization purposes.

Metronome Online also uses cookies to track our affiliates as part of our affiliate program and our advertising efforts. These cookies are placed on your computer and serve to track the commissions and generated sales.

### OPT-IN/OUT OF REQUESTS FOR INFORMATION

We also give users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communication, such as email, from us by sending such a request to [info@metronomeonline.com](mailto:info@metronomeonline.com).  The option to unsubscribe is also available at the end of all of our email communications.

This site also gives users the option to deactivate their account if the user no longer wants to use our services by sending such a request to [info@metronomeonline.com](mailto:info@metronomeonline.com).

### CONTACTING THE WEBSITE

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about Metronome Online privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, please contact us at [info@metronomeonline.com](mailto:info@metronomeonline.com).
